(chuckles) Small world.
(Priya:)You did talk to her, didn't you?
(Leonard:)Of course, I did.
I talked and talked and talked.
(Penny:)Hey! Look at Leonard
in his fancy-ass
grownup clothes.
(Penny:)Way to go, Priya.
For once, he doesn't look
(Penny:)like a mannequin in
the boys' department.
(chuckles)
Hey, did he
(Penny:)tell you I saved
the silk shirt?
(Priya:)No, he did not.
(Penny:)He was gonna throw it
in the washing machine
(Penny:)with his
Spiderman underwear.
(Penny:)That's our Lenny, huh?
(laughs)
(Priya:)Yes, that's our Lenny.
(Penny:)So how's
the food here?
(Penny:)Oh, wow, that is
really, really good.
(Penny:)Oh, I'm sorry.
You guys are on a date.
(Penny:)We can hang out
anytime. Have fun.
(Leonard:)Bye.
Good night.
(Penny:)Oh, that's, hot, hot, hot, hot!
(Penny:)Whoo! It really
sneaks up on ya, huh?
(Penny:)All right, I gotta go.
(Leonard:)It is pretty spicy.